Hi, I'm Tim Gipson, and I'm going to talk to you about how to use a clothes dryer.
Now, before we put our clothes in the dryer, the first thing we want to do is we want to get the lint trap out and we want to run our fingers or this surface, and you want to make sure that you remove any lint.
It's very important to do this every time, otherwise air will not flow properly through your dryer, and your clothes won't get dry.
Or it's going to take a lot more energy to dry your clothes.
So we can replace that lint trap.
We can put our clothes in, and also you want to think you want to be mindful of the capacity of your dryer.
Dryers can come in a regular capacity, a heavy duty capacity, or an extra heavy duty.
And that will determine how many clothes you can actually load in there and properly dry in a cycle.
So once we get our clothes loaded in there and close the door, man, you want to make sure that you choose your right temperature.
A lot of your dryers will come with the temperatures that you can put on low heat for delicates, to a medium heat for knits, or permanent press, all the way up to high heat for your cotton products that are a lot in your regular clothes.